https://logansportsavings.com/bank-info/privacy-disclosure

MENU
Privacy Disclosure
What Does Logansport Savings Bank Do With Your Personal Information?
Why? Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information.
Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What? The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include: Social Security number and income account balances and payment history credit history and credit scores When
you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How? All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons Logansport Savings
Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does Logansport Savings Bank share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes - such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes - to offer our products and services to you
No
We Don't Share
For joint marketing with other financial companies
No
We Don't Share
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your transactions and experiences
No
We Don't Share
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
No
We Don't Share
For nonaffiliates to market to you
No
We Don't Share
Questions? Call (574) 722-3855.
What we do
How does Logansport Savings Bank protect my personal information? To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards, secured files and buildings. We restrict access to nonpublic personal information
about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products and services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information.
How does Logansport Savings Bank collect my personal information? We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Open an account or deposit money
Pay your bills or apply for a loan
Use your debit card
Why can't I limit all sharing? Federal law gives you the right to limit only
Sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
Affiliates from using your information to market to you
Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates - Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. Logansport Savings Bank has no affiliates.
Nonaffiliates - Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. Logansport Savings Bank does not share with nonaffiliates.
Joint marketing - A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you. Logansport Savings Bank does not jointly market.
